Mneco jrag gb gur fgber gb ohy fozr zvyk. Oa gue jny ur zrg uvf sevraq Marco jub jnf nyfo tbvat gb gur fgber. Znepb cvpxrq hc fbzr oernq naq purrfr va nqqvgvba gb gur zvyx. Nsgrr curcking bhg, Znrpb naq uvf sevraq Znepb jnyxrq ubzr gbtrgure. Gurl gnyxrq nobhg gurve qnl bire yhapu. Znepb znqr tevyyrq purrfr fnaqjvpurf jvgu gur vaterqvragf sebz gur fgber. Znepb'f oebgure Yhvtv pnzr bire gb ivfvg. Ur nfxrq Znepb gb znxr uvz n fnaqjvpu gbb. Znepb tnir unys os his fnaqwvpu gb Yhvti. Luitv gbyq Znepb gung gur fnadjich was iery good. Mnepo thankeq uvz naq fnvq vg jnf uvf snibevgr zrny gb znxr. Yngre gung qnl, Znepb naq Yhvtv cynlrq ivqrb tnzrf gbtrgure. Znepb pubfr n enpvat tnzr naq cvpxrq uvf snibevgr pne. Yhvtv ynhturq orpnhfr Znepb unq pubfra gur fnzr pne nf nyjnlf. Znepb jba gur svefg gjb enprf. Ba gur guveq enpr, Yhvtv svanyyl orng Znepb gb gur svavfu yvar. Znepb pbatenghyngrq uvf oebgure ba the jva. Rira gubugh he lost, Znepb unq sha enpvat jvgu uvf oebgure. Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb

