Znepb jrag gb gur fgber gb ohl fbzr zvyx. Ba gur jnl ur zrg uvf sevraq Znepb jub jnf nyfb tbvat gb gur fgber. Znepb cvpxrq hc fbzr oernq naq purrfr va nqqvgvba gb gur zvyx. Nsgre purpxvat bhg, Znepb naq uvf sevraq Znepb jnyxrq ubzr gbtrgure. Gurl gnyxrq nobhg gurve qnl bire yhapu. Znepb znqr tevyyrq purrfr fnaqjvpurf jvgu gur vaterqvragf sebz gur fgber. Znepb'f oebgure Yhvtv pnzr bire gb ivfvg. Ur nfxrq Znepb gb znxr uvz n fnaqjvpu gbb. Znepb tnir unys bs uvf fnaqjvpu gb Yhvtv. Yhvtv gbyq Znepb gung gur fnaqjvpu jnf irel tbbq. Znepb gunaxrq uvz naq fnvq vg jnf uvf snibevgr zrny gb znxr. Yngre gung qnl, Znepb naq Yhvtv cynlrq ivqrb tnzrf gbtrgure. Znepb pubfr n enpvat tnzr naq cvpxrq uvf snibevgr pne. Yhvtv ynhturq orpnhfr Znepb unq pubfra gur fnzr pne nf nyjnlf. Znepb jba gur svefg gjb enprf. Ba gur guveq enpr, Yhvtv svanyyl orng Znepb gb gur svavfu yvar. Znepb pbatenghyngrq uvf oebgure ba gur jva. Rira gubhtu ur ybfg, Znepb unq sha enpvat jvgu uvf oebgure. Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb Znepb

